# PATRICK RAYMOND WONG

www.patrwong.com | +1 718-757-1686 | patrickrwong11@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/patrickrwongjr

## **PROFILE**

Adaptable professional with 10 years of valuable working experience. I have a proven history of successful leadership and effective management, building a positive rapport with various clients and colleagues, and using advanced and creative techniques to achieve company goals. I am seeking to utilize my skills and knowledge to secure a position within your company.

## **EDUCATION**

THE PENNSYLVANIA STATE UNIVERSITY, UNIVERSITY PARK, PA BACHELOR OF ARTS, COMMUNICATIONS – MAY 2011

#### **SKILLS**

- 6 years of Management and Leadership experience overseeing the productivity of others
- 11 years in customer service building repeat clients
- 3 years of Business-to-Consumer Sales experience
- Highly proficient in Salesforce, Zoom, Calendly, MailChimp, Outlook, and Microsoft Office
- Web Development knowledge including HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- Native English, 10 years of Spanish language courses, 2 years of Finnish language courses

#### **EXPERIENCE**

LEAD RECRUITER, SECURITAS; DENVER, CO - APRIL 2019 - FEBRUARY 2020

- Screened and hired qualified candidates for employment utilizing the recruitment process
- Improved the quality of new recruits by revitalizing the previously instated interview process to showcase highly qualified candidates.
- Administered drug testing to abide by the company's Drug Free policy.
- Responsible for implementing on and off-site recruitment fairs to source out potential new hires.

SALES CONSULTANT, TRAVELERS HAVEN; DENVER, CO – JULY 2018 - APRIL 2019

- Converted a high volume of leads into new potential clients using the Salesforce CRM.
- Exceeded daily KPI goals by focusing on building a strong relationship with new customers
- Maintained good organization of my pipeline of clients throughout the sales process.
- Became a top producer in my first month surpassing my colleagues in closed sales by 87%.

TERRITORY MANAGER, TRAVELERS HAVEN; DENVER, CO - JULY 2016 - JULY 2018

- Forged professional connections and brand loyalty by creating a trustworthy partnership with Property Management companies and rental properties across the United States.
- Contributed to reducing company costs by negotiating decreased fees and security deposits.
- Compromised fair and affordable rates to fit budget requests from clients while allowing for Sales consultants to manage margin to reach company goals.

OPERATIONS MANAGER, RIOJA; DENVER, CO - MARCH 2015- JULY 2016

- Supervised a team of 25+ staff members at a James Beard award-winning dining establishment.
- Completed daily duties including interviewing and hiring, revitalizing the training process, professional service education, and performance evaluations of the team-members quarterly.
- Applied creative marketing strategies and utilized social media to draw in new customers and increase business.